Do you believe in karma?
I will never forget the voice that I once heard.
It must've been so funny for you, right?
Well, it's not boring.
If it affected you that much,you must have been secretly filmed before?
If you don't have anything nice to say, just don’t say anything.
How could you make my Jay trust you so much?
You still don't know the first person who founded Dream was?
I never forced you to go.
We can just live like this.
You can use our baby as an excuse to be together.
No, I'm not signing.
No.
I’m leaving.
You need to sign.
Sign this now.
There’s no need to overreact.
If you don't sign it
then I won’t let you leave this room.
Sign it, will you?
That woman, she's waiting for you, isn't she?
Fine.
Are you happy now?
Do you have any idea who’s in the car?
You’re not fucking looking, didn’t you?
Hey!
Just let him go.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
I’m okay.
Okay?
Yes.
Where are you going?
I thought that you were sleeping.
So I don't want to bother you.
I called you up here.
We haven't even talked yet.
You shouldn’t try to avoid me like that.
You’re really…
really like to ignore me, do you?
You like to pretend to be oblivious.
Even though you know damn well that
if you open up to me,
than it is now
You’re talking nonsense again.
See this is exactly you.
You like to push people away,
and also like to say the opposite of what you feel.
Actually,
it’s quite endearing that way.
Although it’s not fun anymore when you keep doing it.
Someday,
you're gonna have to beg me first.
Come sleep with me tonight.
What?
So we can get a little closer.
And this is my way of repaying you, too.
Whatever I give you,
You'll have to take all of it.
Pavinee,
she had to stay with Jay’s father for Jay's sake.
Until Jay is old enough,
so she decided to divorce her husband.
Then came back to Thailand,
to launch an entertainment business like she’s been dreaming of.
Pavinee herself did not have much knowledge of the Thai entertainment industry.
So she needed to rely on the connection of Kongkiat.
Who had more than twenty years of experience in the industry.
At first, everything went well.
But after that Kongkiat did something terrible.
He betrayed her.
Pavinee, I believe your management
has been causing the company’s losses.
What are your plans with the situation?
I'm sorry, ma’am.
In my perspective,
I really think you should consider
stepping down from the CEO.
And just act as a shareholder of the company,
so that the opportunity is available for people to take your place.
Personally, I think that would work better.
For this role in particular,
I would like to nominate Mr.Kongkiat.
Because I think that he has strong leadership
and management skills.
I think you guys really
should just calm down first.
Is everyone agree?
I am.
Me too.
Kongkiat had brought the board members under his influence.
He had convinced everyone
that Pavinee was such an incompetent CEO.
The situation pushed Pavinee to the point that she had
to sell her shares to Kongkiat.
Pavinee felt lost from the betrayal
and she already had pretty bad depression at that time.
Then she decided to…
So?
Do you like my room?
Not at all.
It’s so messy just like your secret office.
Really?
You don’t like it?
Not even a little impressed by it at all?
That old man must’ve told you everything
I was wondering,
why does Sia Jo know so much about you?
He told you so much about me,
why didn't he just tell you everything at once
What do you mean?
The first person
that called me when my mother jumped off the building
was him,
Uncle Jo.
Uncle?
Aright.
Aren't you wondering?
Why am I a partner,
and have an office in Alice’s.
So the people of Dream, they don't know you're the founder’s son?
My mother and I had different last names.
When Mom divorced my Dad and came back to Thailand,
no one knows what her son looked like.
Then I used my fancy degree that I graduated from abroad at my advance
and also with the help of the vice president who is loyal to my mom,
so I was able to get a job there easily as an executive director.
Wanna to eat something?
No.
Steak?
Salad?
Or spaghetti?
Or do you only prefer to eat Pad-Thai?
If you want to eat that, I'll order it.
Do you want it?
How many days have you not been sleeping?
Two days.
No.
Three days.
Three days?
Are you worried about me?
Where's the bedroom?
So what do you want to eat?
I don't want to eat.
Nope.
I’m going to cook for you.
You have to eat mine.
You're this sleepy but still insist on cooking for me?
You need to go to bed now.
Do you eat anything?
Go sleep now.
Come on, just eat something.
I’m not, you need sleep.
I have a question.
When your mother and brother died,
did you cry at all?
Go to sleep now.
Are you not really hungry?
Sleep now.
Go to bed.
Come on.
Sleep, right?
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
Hey?
You?
Dummy?
At least you’re able to sleep.
You’re so damn heavy.
Ouch!
So damn heavy.
Venice, a young actor with a panic attack when there’s a camera facing him.
Yes?
How do you know that I am here?
My debtor is a lot harder to find than you.
We need to talk.
If you’re here to tell me to go back to Dream’s,
you’re wasting your time here.
I'm not going back.
There's nothing I can do now
in the entertainment industry.
Which means you don't want to know
who ruined your audition?
You mean…
someone did that to me on purpose?
If you want to know the truth,
today at five P.M., I’ll see you at studio sixty-seven.
If you're willing to go there,
you’ll find out.
Look at you now.
If you don't care about me,
at least care about someone who genuinely cares about you, like P'Kajorn.
Hello?
You go and wait in the toilet behind Studio Sixty Seven.
Gus, is the coffee for Sunny ready yet?
Not yet. I'll go look it.
Do you have a light roast Ethiopian coffee bean?
No, we don’t.
Next time, you need to have it stand by.
How about this new bean first?
Stop it, whatever Sunny wants, he shall have it.
Excuse me?
I am a huge fan of Sunny.
Yes?
Uhm.. Can you give this letter to Sunny?
I didn’t know that Sunny has such a cute fan boy.
Okay, I'll handle it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Close your eyes.
Can you check if you like the look?
Very handsome.
Clear skin.
Are you okay with the makeup?
Okay?
Momma, let’s go eat.
Where's my coffee?
They couldn’t find it here but
I have someone getting it now.
Next time, write it down alright?
So they know what kind of coffee I usually drink,
it’s annoying that I have to tell you repeatedly.
Right.
Oh, there's a fan asking me to give you this letter.
Here?
How does he know that I’m here?
I don't even know if he's a sasaeng or not?
How dare you accept it?
I don’t think that he’s a sasaeng,
since he just stopped by and left.
He’s a very cute looking fan boy.
Here's the letter.
Close the door on your way out.
I have proof that you ruined my audition.
If you don't want anyone to find out about it,
meet me at the restroom behind the building.
So it’s really you.
So you're going to rat me out?
Fine.
I’d love to see you try.
Loser!
I don't know what proof you have
but I'm not afraid of you.
You are both stupid and couldn't act in front of a camera.
Although you have the gut to threaten me?
Wait a minute, P’Sunny.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Liar!
If you dare call me here like this,
next time it won't just be the camera.
Camera?
So the camera in the audition room was all you?
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
Didn’t you tell me that you have proof?
What proof are you talking about?
Where is it? Give it to me now.
What are you talking about? I don't know.
Are you messing with me?
Who do you think you are?
You're messing with the wrong guy here.
If I want anything,
or I want to get rid of anyone,
I can just call someone and it’ll be done.
Next time, If you still dare to do this
you’ll be dead for sure.
What Sunny did to you was that bad?
He’s fleeing just because he’s seeing you.
See that?
Yes.
It's really what you told me.
There's a movie script
where the character has a panic attack in front of the camera.
I think you would understand this character very well.
So I already asked P’Kajorn to get you the script from the director
It's on you now whether you will take it
or not.
If you’re saying no to it.
What you're gonna lose isn't just an acting career,
but also the opportunity to get revenge.
I'm not sure becoming an actor for revenge is really a good idea.
But I will go back
for P’Kajorn.
And why do you have to help me this much?
I thought you didn't really like me very much.
Why did you think that?
Well, Mr. Sun doesn't look okay,
When I called P’Sun.
Black coffee, no sugar.
Whoa, P’sun.
Don't call me P’Sun.
Just calling me Sun is enough.
That’s not the reason.
It’s not because I don’t like you.
You just...
It just reminds me of my dead brother.
I’m so sorry.
From now on you can call me whatever you want.
That’d be nice.
P’Sun.
Welcome back, my little bro!
Sorry, I've been gone for a long time.
It's completely fine.
Everyone has to deal with problems of their own.
Although once you reach my age things will be tougher.
Mid life crisis, you know?
But I don't want any more problems in my life.
The problem will only make us grow.
Ready?
Ready to meet the director?
Very much ready.
Great, so let's go.
Let's go!
Thank you.
Be comfortable, don’t stress.
You two don’t get too excited, okay?
Alright.
Hello.
Hello P’Kajorn.
I brought these kids to cast for your short film.
This is Sky,
and this is Sun.
In case there is a suitable role for him  to try to audition.
Everyone, this is P'Karn, the Director.
Hello.
So is this Sky the person that you mentioned before?
- Yes.
Okay, so have you read the script?
- I read it.
- He read it.
Then why don’t we try acting it out?
And you?
He’s Sun.
Nun!
Could you bring the script of the character Danai for Sun to try out?
Here, read it first and you can try and cast this character.
Thank you.
Sky, this way please.
Please.
Okay, according to the script,
this character sees the camera and feels scared.
If what's written here is true,
Then my entire kingdom fell for it.
I don't want to know.
Breathe slowly.
Take a deep breath
Focus on the present.
Thank you.
You don’t have any knife with you, right?
Alright.
Come in, please.
I’m walking to the edge of the building
which is my goal for today.
What we needed to do,
we have accomplished it all.
Can I have another round? And try to give a little more meaning into it?
And then look at me instead, don’t look at the camera.
It’s like you’re talking to me.
Start whenever you’re ready.
Right now I’m walking to the edge of the building
which is my goal for today.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
For Sky,
I think that Sky is quite suitable for this role.
Not sure if you are okay if I want him to take the role.
I’m completely okay with that.
In fact, I’m very pleased.
Thank you so much.
I’m open to negotiating the rates as well.
Oh, thank you.
Then I'll have my team get you the contract.
And if there’s anything that isn’t okay you can discuss with me.
Okay, then I'll read it as soon as possible.
Thank you.
What about Sun?
Um, well, I think that he has the potential to be a good actor,
but you probably have to wait for him to be ready a little more.
I think there is a chance that he could go far.
Right.
P’Kajorn,
where did you get this script from?
Why is that?
Honestly, this project has almost been canceled.
Only the current investors know about the script.
And who is the investor?
The executive director of Dream’s?
Director Arthur.
Yes, yes, that’s right, Director Arthur.
Hello?
Teemekha, come here now.
Sun, can I ask you this, what exactly is going
on between you and Director Arthur?
Just an acquaintance.
I mean, I didn't want to think you two were…
And that’s why you got all kinds of privileges.
Hey!
I knew you came here for revenge,
but you don't have to become an actor like Sunny.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I know what I'm doing.
I'm just worried about you.
Whatever you do, you need to think carefully.
Thank you for today. Don't hesitate to contact me anytime.
Yes, thank you.
Please, have a drink.
So the Memory the series is scheduled to start filming
at the end of the year right?
Well, if nothing goes wrong,
it should be scheduled at the end of the year.
I'm investing a lot of money into that series,
but the answer I got was “it should be”.
I'm looking for the right person, sir.
A good things takes time, sir.
But I can ensure you that
everything will be done on the timeline, of course.
This is Dream's new trainee.
In case you want to give him a chance.
If you want to have a future,
how about you use your mouth to navigate your future.
Kongkiat sir,
Can I talk to you outside?
I want to get rid of the trainee named Sun.
You can do whatever so that he can’t be in the industry.
You really do nothing all day.
Aside from wanting to get rid of people.
Although what did this trainee do to you?
I used to borrow money from him before I entered the industry.
I don't get why he's so full of resentment.
He won’t stop harassing me.
Why don’t you just give the money back to him?
I don't have time to handle these little things for you.
Can't you see?
That I have to deal with The memory project
so that it sails smoothly without any thorns in the side.
Otherwise, you won't be playing as the main protagonist.
Does this project have a thorn in the side?
This is the overall mood and tone.
Thank you.
Yes.
Then how about Sky go and get changed your clothes first.
Alright, will do.
It's really incredible that we'll be working on Mr. Pakin for the second time.
What's wrong?
Excited?
Be confident!
You’re going to be shining today.
Wanna try this?
Go like this.
Hello, P’Kajorn.
Hello.
How are you? Excited?
Ready?
So ready!
Then wait here for a second, alright?
I think it should be there.
Pakin.
Yes?
Thank you so much for helping me today.
It's alright, P'Karn.
Your project really challenges my ability,
so how can I say no to you?
Sure, sure.
Come here, I want to introduce the actors to you.
Yeah, right.
This is Sky  will be playing as Venice.
Sky?
Are you going to be okay, today?
Don't waste my time!
How is it?
Please take care of it for me.
Just forget about him.
You should go and get change now.
Yes.
ใช่ค่ะ
Very pretty.
We got 2 pictures.
You’re ready, right?
This way, please.
Okay.
Please over there.
Ready?
Turn your face to the right a little.
I said right.
My right.
Isn't Venice a character that is afraid of cameras?
Can you show me through the eyes?
How are you going to do it?
This isn’t working.
I'll let him look at the camera first.
Alrighty.
Turn and look at the camera.
What are you doing?
They’re in the middle of a photoshoot, you’ll get yelled at.
Just like that.
Turn to the side.
Turn to the right now.
Okay.
I think we’re done.
Sky, please come for the interview.
Can I take some videos for behind the scenes?
How do you feel? Nervous?
How are you?
How do you feel that you get the role as Venice?
Are you excited?
I
That's enough.
Please stop.
I'm really sorry.
Is he putting on an act for us?
Wow, very convincing!
That's enough.
I’m really sorry.
Please let me go. I’m begging you.
Let me go please.
I'm sorry.
Quit filming.
I think we should leave for now.
There's no camera now.
Sky, we have cleared the cameras out.
Please, stop filming me. I’m begging you.
Get the cameras out please, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Did you know prior to this that he has these symptoms?
You mean me?
Yeah, you.
Normally, Sky likes to get really nervous in front of the camera,
So I mostly assigned him to the stage plays.
This is not just nervousness.
He is really sick.
What kind of manager are you?
Why don't you know how sick he is?
Don't blame P'Kajorn.
It's fully my fault.
I never told anyone.
Do you really have a panic attack?
Then let's go check the photos inside.
Are you really alright?
Thank you for asking.
Sky,
you…
you have a panic attack?
I actually don't know either.
But every time I knew that the camera was shooting me,
I saw them.
I couldn’t control myself.
I wanted to get away from there, but I couldn't move.
What did you see?
I was forced to take videos by my seniors.
There were a few seniors
waited for me in front of the restroom.
Hey, you see seniors and don't care to greet us?
Smiling, will you?
Hey, where do you think you’re going?
Where are you going?
I told you to greet me respectfully but you did nothing.
Why don't you pay respect to seniors?
Should we beat him up?
What are you waiting for?
Do it.
When I finished using the restroom, all of a sudden they…
Come on.
Let me go, please.
Let me see what’s inside.
Hold him still.
They took off my clothes.
That's enough, I'm sorry.
Help me. Help me.
No one can help you.
There was one person holding a camera
filming  me.
No one can help you.
Please, don’t.
I was saying sorry to them.
Please don’t.
I'm really sorry
Let me go.
Please, just let me go.
He said that it was because I didn’t pay respect to him.
You look at me, will you?
Look up a little.
I told them that I’m sorry and please let me go.
Although it didn’t work.
But that’s okay,
it was such a long time ago.
I'm sorry, Sky.
I'm really sorry.
I really do sorry.
Let's go see a therapist together, alright?
It's alright.
I think today I’m getting better just being able to get it out with you guys.
And why would you apologize to me?
You did nothing wrong.
Are you able to be filmed in this movie?
I have to do it.
How about this?
Next time you see those damn faces again,
why don’t you imagine their faces as mine instead?
I think it will be scarier then.
How about P'Kajorn face then?
I can't do that.
We'll go see the doctor.
Don't you worry about the movie.
We both will take care of you here.
But most importantly,
whatever issues you’re having,
you have to let me know everything.
Okay.
Thank you.
Why are you responding so slowly?
Are you working?
Now you prioritize work over me?
You're gonna have to sleep with me again tonight.
I can’t, I have to work early tomorrow.
Since you prioritize work over me
then I'll go to my job, too.
I have a meeting anyway.
Finally.
What's wrong?
Are you talking to a spirit around here?
For the project in the last quarter of this year.
It's a mega project called The Memory the Series.
It was a film that grossed over 500 million baht last year.
It made every cast member an overnight sensation.
And Dream Company has already purchased the rights
to turn into a series adaptation version of the movie.
Starring Mr. Sunny T้hanaphat.
I think there are more people that are a better fit than Sunny.
Like PEN-NUENG.
PEN-NUENG is our agency's number one star right now.
But we have to think about the future too.
If we don't groom any new talent
then our company can't grow.
I agree.
If we look at the marketing aspects,
PEN-NUENG has been well used.
And now Sunny is our rising star.
I understand your vision.
But I think…
We should look at who is better suited to this character.
This is more about the main sponsor of this movie.
Also the platform of customers who want someone fresh.
They want to tap into the teen market.
So Sunny would be the best choice.
As far as I've searched,
More than eighty percent of PEN-NUENG fans are in their teens
to working-age adults.
Which means they have socials to help with the trending,
and money to support his work.
The reason that I’m saying all this
is because I really mean well.
So I want you to reconsider if the main actor
Except that,
you chose Sunny for reasons other
than his suitability for the role.
I'm telling you now.
It has to be Sunny because the sponsor has asked for him.
You're still a rookie in the entertainment business.
Damn it!
President, don't worry, sir.
The ultimate decision is still yours anyway.
That kid is trying to embarrass me in front of everyone.
He’s being so cocky,
just because he’s having some good business connections.
He must think that he's a hotshot around here.
What will you do next?
I must get rid of him, of course.
Completely get rid of him.
This is the fifth scene.
Yes.
Right here, I'll close it off and try to create a new light.
Okay.
It will be smooter.
What is this?
It's a mirror.
Yeah, the mirror.
Let me set up the scene first so we'll make it before the break.
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
Then please take care of it.
How are you, Sky?
I’m trying not to be nervous but I am quite nervous now.
If Sky can't do it, you have to tell me.
And after you’re done with the scene,
try and get out of the character as soon as possible.
Copy that.
Come on.
Yes, I said that.
Come on out, clear out of the scene.
The hairdressers and the makeup artists come out now, they are pretty enough.
Let’s go.
Everyone, clear the set.
Okay, keep your voice down.
Sound!
Camera!
And set!
And Action!
Thank you so much.
Without you,
I must have believed those deceptions.
It's okay, sir. I'm willing to do so.
Nuan,
I...
Venice, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I can't do it.
I just can’t.
Venice, why don’t you try first?
Are you okay?
I can't.
I can't do it.
Venice, you can do it.
You have to beat it.
Otherwise, you'll never get another chance to be in front of the camera.
I can't.
I truly can't.
I really can't.
Cut!
Very good, Sky
Everyone, clear the set. Clear the set.
Ah, let’s go this way.
Nicely done!
Go.
Are you alright?
Why don’t you do that relaxation exercise?
The one that you taught me.
Hey!
Ouch! That hurts
It’s hurting me.
Hey, Sun!
You’re hurting me.
Sun!
It really hurt, P’Sun.
What are you doing?
Okay now?
I am.
I’m okay now.
Do you want another round?
That's enough.
It’s good that you’re better.
Then I'll be right back.
Breathe.
Relaxation tion.
Deep breath.
Thank you.
To the brother who has recovered from camera phobia.
Yeah!
I haven't recovered yet.
I think it’s going to take a lot of time.
Today I almost got in trouble.
Um,
As long as you don't pass out before they call cut,
I would consider that success.
You know, I'm really proud of you.
And how about Angie?
How can you keep drinking?
Oh! I dropped her off with her grandparents today.
It's been a while since I drank with you guys.
Cheer!
And today, I want to thank you too.
Without you, it could’ve been bad.
Next time, I'll use your service again.
But please be a little gentler.
It was very painful.
The more frequently you depend on my help, the harsher I’ll be.
Next time, your bones will be broken.
You’re a really tough guy, aren’t you?
Give me your glass, I’ll get you more ice.
Let me handle that.
Hello, what’s up, Poy?
Trending No.1?
Wait a moment, let me see first.
What’s happening?
PEN-NUENG’s in trouble.
And now people in the company are
demanding director Arthur
to resign from Dream’s.
They rumored that you’re the one who leaked the news about PEN-NUENG.
The man who committed the offense in this incident is…
We will take the most decisive action.
If you don't think about doing anything now
then you prepare to collapse, and there’s no going back.
I told you to leave.
The sound of your heart is beating so loud.
You keep thinking about your mistakes.
Until you refused to face your identity for five years.
Please make me cry.